(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T10:10:41.703118",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
What?
Hi everyone!
Oh, I see all of your comments!
Hi! How are you?
What time is it?
It's Tako time!
Hi everyone!
How are you guys doing?
Are you live?
Wait.
Well, first of all, one thing I, you know, promised you guys
was to kabedon as soon as got the 3D showcase, so...
was to kabedon as soon as I got the 3D showcase, so...
Kabedon!
Oya oya, Takodachi, what are you doing here?
Oh my, Takodachi, what are you doing here?
Oh no, I was so, so, so, so nervous, but you know, let's just...
let's just do it normally, normally. Hi!
Hi everyone!
Isn't it so exciting?
We waited so, so long for this to finally happen, and uh...
We waited so, so long for this to finally happen, and um...
it's finally here, it's finally here!
I can't I can't contain my excitement, I'm sorry.
I can't—I can't contain my excitement, I'm sorry.
You know, I'm going first, you know, usually for relays we ended up with, you know, the debut order.
But this time for special, special event, I'm the first one to go.
But this time for a special, special event, I'm the first one to go.
So I'll do my best, but make sure you check out the others, uh 3D showcases coming up in the upcoming weeks too.
So I'll do my best, but make sure you check out the others' 3D showcases coming up in the upcoming weeks too!
Yay! But yeah.
Well, first of all, I guess I can show you guys around the place, maybe? Maybe? Yeah, okay.
Come on you guys, follow me, follow me. Yeah!
So, you guys are maybe a little bit familiar with this place, you know, there's some art supplies, you know,
my little drawing workspace. Oh! I guess I haven't really shown you guys how I do traditional art, but...
someone's familiar. Could it be?
Outchou! It's...
Out-chan! It's...
Ao-chan!
in the flesh.
Ao-chan's sleeping right now, but
I guess you heard of Ina's back.
How about Ao-chan's back?
I guess you don't really see Ao-chan's back that often. Hey!
You don't really see Ao-chan's back that often, eh?
But apparently, the TV drama has been decided on, but you know, I think it's still in the works.
But apparently, a TV drama has been decided, but you know, I think it's still in the works.
But yes, Ao-chan!
And I guess you can look around the rest of the room.
Well, here's my little bookshelf area. It's not full of books yet, but there's a couch over there I usually like to sleep on, you know. I sleep everywhere.
And yeah, some miscellaneous things. And of course, can't forget my streaming desk. That's right.
And yeah, some miscellaneous things. And of course, I can't forget my streaming desk, that's right!
I stream from here, you know. I go, "Hi guys!" And you guys see, see the, you know, the view behind me. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I stream from here, you know. I go, "Hi guys!" And you guys see the view behind me. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then if we walk over a little more this way, you get to see, more books. I love books.
But then there's like a beautiful garden out there. You guys don't really get to see this often, right?
But then there's a beautiful garden out there. You guys don't really get to see this often, right?
Yeah. And of course, can't forget this angle of the room, which you guys are very familiar with. Yay! This is my little studio. What do you guys think? Isn't it great?
Yeah, I'm so exciting.
Yeah, I'm so excited!
Yeah, you know, I really want to show you guys, you know, this whole space and finally after what, two, two and a half, maybe two and a half, two years-ish, yeah. Um, yeah, I'm so, so happy.
Yeah, you know, I really wanted to show you guys, you know, this whole space, and finally after what, two, two and a half... maybe two and a half, two years-ish, yeah. Um, yeah, I'm so, so happy.
I'm losing my vocabulary here because I'm so, so nervous and happy and just flooded with ocean sigh.
I'm losing my vocabulary here, because I'm so, so nervous and happy, and just flooded with emotions.
But I guess, um, there's one thing you guys have been looking forward to when it comes to 3D streams, huh?
Something I haven't shown you guys yet. I mean, I've appeared in lives, I've appeared in different shows and programs in my 3D. There's one thing, one thing I've asked to keep secret until today.
What do you think it is? What could it be?
That's right! My tentacles! Ina's boing boings. But you know, it's it's a little, it's a little embarrassing.
That's right! My tentacles! Ina's boing-boings. But you know, it's a little, it's a little embarrassing.
Look, let me look away a little bit. Just look away a little bit. Okay.
Look, let me look away a little bit. Let me look away a little bit. Okay.
Are you guys ready? Wait, tada! Ina boing-boing.
It's boing-boing! It's right, I told you guys, it's not, it's not attached to my back. There's like a void gate in there somewhere that there's summoned from, but boing-boing!
It's boing-boing! That's right, I told you guys, it's not, it's not attached to my back! There's like a void gate in there somewhere that they're summoned from, but boing-boing!
Are they so... I want to touch. Don't you just want to squeeze them? You can't!
Are they so... I want to touch them. Don't you just want to squeeze them? You can't!
But they're boing boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing!
But they're boing-boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing!
Yeah. Oh. Okay, calm down, you know, calm down. You'll be okay.
What you guys think? Yay!
What do you guys think? Yay!
Ah, tentacles, you're kind of in the way.
Okay, look away for a second. Look away for a second.
Wait.
Okay, we good.
Okay, we're good.
We got a message for me? Oh my goodness!
A challenge. Hmm, what could they have cooked up for me? Well, they sent in some messages for me, so,
let's see, let's see, uh, what they have. Okay, let's start with Kiara.
let's see, let's see what they have. Okay, let's start with Kiara.
Hello everybody, this is Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English. First of all, congratulations on being number one for the brain-
It's okay. Let's go. I am going fine right now. No, hopefully. I'm scared.
It's okay. Let's go! I am doing fine right now. No, hopefully. I'm scared.
I am here to request a pose or two from you. So, let me start, uh, I want two things. Let me start with, I want your best or your cutest idol pose.
Idol pose, idol pose in 5 seconds. I can give you 5 seconds to think.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, go!
Cute! Cute! Okay, okay. Here we go again. Next one.
instructions for camera
Yeah, and now, Ina, put your hands together like you're praying, okay?
and do a pouty face.
As if you're asking the viewer for some something.
As if you're asking the viewer for something...
Could you be like, "Onegaigan"
credit card number, please?
Keep on doing that.
All right, bye-bye!
Bye Kiara, thank you!
Yeah, you know, Kiara flew over to, uh, you know, somewhere else for now.
Yeah, Kiara flew over to, uh, somewhere else for now.
But yeah, thank you Kiara, ah, idol pose.
Thank you, Kiara. Ah, idol pose.
Idol pose is always difficult, you know, but I'll try.
Idol poses are always difficult, you know, but I'll try.
Okay, what do we have next? Ame!
Hi, Ina! I'm so proud of you!
Oh, proud of me! I know it takes a lot of courage to get up and do this stuff in front of a lot of people.
Oh, proud of me! I know it takes courage to do this in front of people.
You've finally made it! Yay!
I love watching you move and wave around the things you do with your arms and walk.
I love watching you move and wave your arms around.
You know, I already know, you look so cute doing it, too.
I already know you look so cute doing it, too.
So, Ame's request is first, you gotta plank.
That's right, you gotta get down on the ground and do that trend that people did a long time ago.
You gotta get down on the ground and do that old trend.
Cuz this is just the first step, okay?
Okay, I'll wait. Are you there yet?
Okay, okay. Then, if staff doesn't yell at you, you gotta do the worm!
Okay, okay. Then, if staff doesn't yell at you, do the worm!
Oh no, staff-san is yelling at me, it seems I cannot do the worm.
Oh no, staff-san is yelling at me. I can't do the worm.
Okay, I can I can do this though, I can I guess, is it more of like a full body wave?
Okay, I can do this though. Is it more of a full body wave?
Yeah, yeah. Inana, how are your arms, tentacle hairs? And that backbone?
Yeah, yeah. Inana, how are your arms, tentacle hair, and backbone?
Well, that wasn't too difficult of a pose.
Thank you, Ina! Bye-bye! Love you!
She- she she don't see. I love you, Ame! I love you!
She doesn't see. I love you, Ame! I love you!
Oh, Ame, oh, Ame is so cute. I can't wait to see her 3D as well.
Oh, Ame is so cute. I can't wait to see her 3D as well.
Okay, who do we have next?
Oh, from Calli! Ah, hello there, Ina, Ina, Ina, it's me, your- your boy, your reaper, Calliope Mori
Oh, from Calli! Hello there, Ina. It's me, your boy, your reaper, Calliope Mori,
of the myth generation, same as you. Wow.
Oh man, I have a lot to say, but I feel like, um, it might end up being redundant or unnecessary.
Oh man, I have a lot to say, but I feel like it might be redundant.
So, um, I'm just gonna say thanks for being a shoulder for me to lean on.
So I'll just say thanks for being a shoulder for me to lean on.
Quite literally sometimes, um, we've had so much fun together between Guilty Gear Strive and- and playing recorders together.
Quite literally sometimes. We've had so much fun playing Guilty Gear Strive and recorders together.
And hopefully soon we can do the ukulele thing, but until then, I just want to let you know that, uh, you're a great friend that I can always depend upon.
And hopefully soon we can do ukulele, but you're a great friend I can always depend on.
And I never feel weird talking to you ever, like, um, it's always really chill and laid back.
I never feel weird talking to you; it's always really chill and laid back.
And I think it's because you remind me of, um, my- my art friends from the past.
And I think it's because you remind me of my art friends from the past.
So you're a very important person to me, um,
So you're a very important person to me,
and so, uh, since I feel so comfortable around you, I'm gonna ask you to do some poses that make you feel uncomfortable.
and since I feel so comfortable around you, I'm gonna ask you to do some uncomfortable poses.
But not in like a weird way, like, in a- in like a way where like it's hard for you to do them.
Not in a weird way, but in a way where it's hard for you to do them.
Because everybody here is going to be asking you to do like cute things, I'm sure, right?
Because everybody's going to ask you to do cute things, right?
Well, I'm here to dish out the real challenges.
Um, so I'm gonna ask you to do, uh, the worm.
So I'm gonna ask you to do... the worm.
I'm guessing the worm- Yeah, the worm might be a little difficult for you, but I- I want to see you put your back into it.
The worm might be a difficult, but I want to see you put your back into it.
You know? Give it your all. But in the event that you can't do the worm, that's okay.
Give it your all. But if you can't do the worm, that's okay.
I've prepared a second choice: You may choose between the worm or the splits.
I've prepared a second choice: the worm or the splits.
She's- she's gonna get me back for this one, isn't she? Oh god.
She's gonna get me back for this one, isn't she? Oh god.
Just you wait, Calliope Mori, I should- I should be nicer to- to little- to these because she's the first one debuting 3D.
Just you wait, Calli! I should be nicer since she's the first one debuting 3D.
Oh man, I'm gonna be in big trouble.
Okay, look, Ina-
Okay, look, Ina—
Splits are good for you.
Are they? They can be good for you. For your health.
They can be good for you. For your health.
Make you flexible, right?
That's not in my dictionary.
You'll- you'll thank me later.
You'll thank me later.
Okay, I'll try not to stretch your muscles too bad, whichever one you choose, okay?
I'll try not to stretch your muscles too bad whichever you choose, okay?
That's not very good, though. Not quite as good as Gura, but still, you can count on me.
That's not quite as good as Gura, but still, you can count on me.
Just like I can count on you. Good luck!
Thank you, Calli! Oh, she disappeared.
Well, I can't do the worm, so I'll- I'll try the splits. I'll try the splits.
Well, I can't do the worm, so I'll try the splits.
Okay, wait. That's it. This is as far as it can go.
See, I'm not that flexible. See, I can't... Oh yeah, I can't touch my toes.
Okay, that's as far as... That's as far as...
I'm sorry, I tried. I tried, tried, I tried. I practiced, but I just can't touch my toes.
But okay, we have I think we have one last, one last message,
Okay, we have—I think we have one last, one last message,
um from Gumba... Gura.
um, from Gumba—Gura.
Hi Ina!
Gura!
Ina!
I want to watch you do the... Oh sure, Marine de suū.
Good luck with the rest of your 3D showcase.
Love you, Ina!
Hokku ra hatto!
Ah... Oh, oshō marīn desu.
How do I do this? How does Gura do it? Chat, chat, I didn't I don't know how.
How do I do this? How does Gura do it? Chat, chat, I don't know how.
Hororaibu sankisei, oshō, marīn desu.
Hololive 3rd Gen, Oshou, Marine desu.
Senchou, sumimasen. Sumimasen.
Senchou, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oshou marīnde sū. Yeah!
Okay, I'll I'll I'll I'll practice this later. Thank you! Sorry, sorry Senchou.
Okay, I'll practice this later. Thank you! Sorry, sorry Senchou.
But yeah, that was that was the call from from Myth.
But yeah, that was that was the call from Myth.
Oh, they're honestly without them I I really I
Oh, they're honestly... Without them, I really—
I mean we couldn't be here without each other. So I'm really really happy they're my gen mates and
I mean, we couldn't be here without each other. So I'm really, really happy they're my gen mates,
that we can finally show you guys our 3D showcases.
and that we can finally show you guys our 3D showcases.
Thank you and and and you guys too, that you guys, you know, this would not happen possible.
Thank you! And and you guys too—without you guys, you know, this would not be possible.
So thank you very much. Thank you, thank you.
Well, you know, we've kind of warmed up now. I think we can probably move on to something special like prepared for you guys.
Well, you know, we've kind of warmed up now. I think we can probably move on to something special prepared for you guys.
So you guys are curious how I, you know, craft things from the void.
This time to make it easier for you to understand, I prepared a magical canvas where I can draw something, I can use it as a catalyst,
This time, to make it easier for you to understand, I prepared a magical canvas where I can draw something I can use as a catalyst,
that's right. Catalyst to summon whatever I draw. Surprise!
that's right—a catalyst to summon whatever I draw. Surprise!
Okay, let's uh let's let's go over there and bring the canvas over.
Okay, let's uh let's go over there and bring the canvas over.
Here is my canvas. Oishou! It's pretty heavy, but I've been practicing.
Blank canvas isn't that so scary? Number one, you know, things artists fear.
But let me just grab this magical brush here. Hoi! Isn't this brush really big?
I don't know how well I can draw with this, but uh
How about we test out the canvas for a bit, okay? I actually haven't tested if it works.
So I'll just draw something really quick. A smile in in ring. In ring and done!
So I'll just draw something really quick. A smile, in-ring, in-ring, and done!
Speed paint! Who's that?
Who's that? Who's that cutie on the canvas?
It's you!
Okay, okay, let me just put down my brush. Oishou! So I prepared a special summoning room just for this occasion.
So I'll just uh bring you guys right on over. Oishou! Oishou! Okay, let's go.
All right. I'll put you guys on.
Okay, are you guys ready? There's a saying amongst artists, if you draw what you want from the gacha, you shall you shall get it.
Okay, are you guys ready? There's a saying among artists: if you draw what you want from the gacha, you shall you shall get it.
So it's also called kakeba deru. So that'll be our magical spell today. Are you guys ready?
Kakeba deru!
That was great!
Tako...
Tako, you mean it?
Oh, I have to be careful. I don't... I don't step on any of you.
Tako! Oh, you're so cute!
You know it was my dream, you know, that you guys joined me on a special day.
Tako!
Tako! Ah, you're so cute!
Hi! Oi!
Hi! Hey!
Face! Oi!
Face! Hey!
Say hi!
Ah, you guys are so cute!
Look at you!
Hi!
Wait!
Seems... seems a little empty. Hmm, odd.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Yeah, Tako!
It succeeded. Okay, so the canvas works.
The magical canvas works, so I'll just... Actually, I'm kidding.
I'll let you guys go.
There you go.
And since that worked, you know, special occasion...
Maybe, just maybe, if we draw a Hololive member, do you think they'll be summoned as well?
Well, we'll give it a try.
Okay, okay, okay. Get my special brush.
All right, who should I draw first?
Oh, I know, I know. There's no mistaking this member.
I'm sure you guys will guess right away.
Just to make sure, I'll write this.
Done with my brush.
Phew! Let me hear ya.
Who could it be, chat? Who could it be?
Can you guess?
We have a cup here and some wings and the word "BAN".
Hmm. Who could it be? Well...
Take you to the summoning room.
I should have built the summoning room a little closer to the studio.
Okay, here we go.
Gibadidoo!
Yozora Mel! Yay!
Mel-senpai!
Yay!
Yay! Cute!
あの、ところでさ、これ何これ？えー、カップ、カップですかね？
Um, by the way, what is this? Eh, a cup? Is this a cup?
これ、メル、これメルってこと？カップ？うーん、うん、うん、え？
This is Mel? This is Mel? A cup? Hmm, um, um, eh?
先輩じゃなくて、なんか先輩を召喚するためになんか…
It's not senpai, it's something I made to summon senpai...
メルの顔を描こうと思っちゃったよ。うん、うん、うん。
I thought about drawing Mel's face. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
あ、と、ど、どうしても、文字はちょっとあの、大丈夫です。消さないでください。
Ah, do- do- don't worry about the letters, it's okay. Please don't erase it.
BAN。
BAN.
いや、BANだめでしょう！BANだめでしょうせっかくのお披露目なのに！
No, BAN is no good! BAN is no good, even though it's a grand debut reveal!
BANはだめだよ！メル様もちょっと…
BAN is no good! Mel-senpai is also a bit...
だめ、だめ。
No, no.
だめ。だめ。だめだめ！だめだめ！
No. No. No no! No no!
いや、いな、thanks for joining me today, Mel-senpai,来てくださってありがとうございます！
Yeah, Ina, thanks for joining me today, Mel-senpai, thank you for coming!
いや、こちらこそありがとうございます！いな、おめでとう！ありがとうございます！
No, thank you as well! Congratulations, Ina! Thank you very much!
いや、メル先輩は最初の、えー、先輩、私が出会った…
You see, Mel-senpai was the first senpai I met when I visited Japan.
So, you know, when when I met her, I was like, "Senpai, please, please, you know, I would love you to take part in the 3D Ohiro-me stream."
So, you know, when I met her, I was like, "Senpai, please, please, you know, I would love you to take part in the 3D Ohiro-me stream."
And she said yes right away! I'm so happy!
Thank you!
せっかくだからなんか一緒に撮ろうよ写真。
Since we're here, let's take a photo together.
あ、写真？うん。
Ah, a photo? Yeah.
スクショタイム！スクショ！どうします？こここんな感じ、かわいい、BAN。
Screenshot time! Screenshot! What should we do? Like this, cute, BAN.
BANだめですよ！
BAN is no good!
かわいい、BANって何だ？でも、かわいい。ねえ先輩かわいい。
Cute, what's "BAN"? But cute. Hey senpai, cute.
いな、いな、キューーーート！やったー！やったー！
Ina, Ina, cuuuute! Yay! Yay!
うわー！嬉しい先輩！先輩のカップ…
Wow! I'm so happy, senpai! Senpai's cup...
先輩のカップ？あ、そう、先輩のカップ…
Senpai's cup? Ah, yes, senpai's cup...
だめだめだめ！だめだめ！
No no no! No no!
大丈夫、大丈夫。先輩そうそう…
It's okay, it's okay. Senpai, that's right...
あ、そう？すごいソフト。ソフトなの？柔らかいってこと？
Oh really? So soft. Soft? You mean soft?
めっちゃ、めっちゃかわいい！
Super, super cute!
いな、いなもキューーーート！やったー！
Ina, Ina is also cuuuute! Yay!
かわいい、いな。
Cute, Ina.
Yeah, thank you so much for joining me today.
Let's let's collab again, let's play more. Still here, collab, みなさんありがとうございます！
Let's let's collab again, let's play more. Still here, collab, thank you everyone!
Thank you! みなさんどうもありがとうございます！キューーート！
Thank you! Thank you everyone so much! Cuuuute!
それじゃ…
Well then...
めるは仲間に帰るかな？
Is Meru going back to her friends?
うん
Yeah.
いなすけ アイラブユー！愛してるー！
Inasuke, I love you! I love you!
またね、みんなもー！バイバーイ！
See you later, everyone! Bye-bye!
はー、める先輩
Ah, Mel-senpai...
ソーキュート
is so cute!
I can't handle it, my heart is melting.
Since we know that, uh, we can successfully summon some other members...
Since we know that we can successfully summon other members...
There is another member I do want to try and summon, you know? Maybe you guys will know who she is right away.
There's another member I do want to try and summon, you know? Maybe you guys will know who she is right away.
Let me grab my brush. Oishotta!
Let me grab my brush. Heave-ho!
All right, I'm ready. Speed painting time!
There's no way, like, I can get this wrong, right? So, so, so easy to draw. Hook, hook, hook, hook, and little scarf.
There's no way I can get this wrong, right? So, so, so easy to draw. Hook, hook, hook, hook, and a little scarf.
Okay, done!
Can you guys guess who it is? Who could it be? Who could it be?
To the summoning room!
Let's go, let's go! Heave-ho, hee-ho, ha!
かけば出る。かけば出る！
If I draw it, she'll appear. If I draw it, she'll appear!
雪花ラミィ？
Yukihana Lamy?
え？誰？
Eh? Who?
ラミィ？
Lamy?
え、どうし？え、ラミィ？あ、どうし？
Eh, what's—eh, Lamy? Ah, what's happening?
ラミィ？あ、I'm Lamy?
Lamy? Ah, I'm Lamy?
ラミィ？え？
Lamy? Eh?
ラミィ？お？
Lamy? Oh?
あ、お前、お？
Ah, you are, oh?
オッケーオッケーオッケー。ハグミーハグミーハグミー！オッケー！ハグミー！おちゅちゅちゅちゅちゅちゅ。マイ、いな、いなちゅ、
Okay, okay, okay. Hug me, hug me, hug me! Okay! Hug me! Chu-chu-chu-chu-chu-chu. My Ina, Inachu...
あ！
Ah!
だめだ！
No good!
なめなめなめなめ。ラミィ！ラミィ、の、の、の、の、の、の！
No, no, no, no! Lamy! Lamy, no, no, no, no, no, no!
オッケーオッケー、I'll try again. I'll try again. I think I messed up. I think I messed up here.
Okay, okay, I'll try again. I'll try again. I think I messed up. I think I messed up here.
Okay, go back down, go back down. Okay.
Seems like, um, I have to be a little more specific when I draw.
Seems like I have to be a little more specific when I draw.
ぁ…
Ah...
All right, let me try again. Let me try again. All right, let me grab my brush.
I'll actually be more specific when I draw this time. All right, all right, right. I draw Lamy's cute face here, her hair, her flower, smile.
I'll actually be more specific when I draw this time. All right, right, right. I'll draw Lamy's cute face here, her hair, her flower, her smile.
And done! Okay.
How's this painting? I think I think I stepped up my speedpainting.
All right, let me just put this down. All right, I gotta save Lamy from being stuck in another floor. All right, let's go.
All right, let me just put this down. All right, I gotta save Lamy from being stuck on another floor. All right, let's go.
たたたたたたた、Lamy!
Tatatatata, Lamy!
I'll save you, Lamy!
Okay, done. All right. Surely, surely it'll work. I drew—I drew her more detailed this time, so
かけば出る！
if I draw her, she'll appear!
わぁ！やったぁ！ラミィだよ！ありがとう、いなすけぇ！オープンシーズニィー！
Wah! Yay! It's Lamy! Thank you, Inasuke! Open Season Niki!
あ！いなすけ！ラミィ！ラミィ！
Ah! Inasuke! Lamy! Lamy!
さっきのラミィ？
Lamy from earlier?
えぇ、さっきちょっとあの失敗した、大福がちょっと、あの、大福がちょっと、あの、おっ… (giggles) ごめん、ごめんごめんなさい。
Eh, earlier I made a bit of a—a mistake, and Daifuku was a bit—um, Daifuku was a bit, um... Oh, sorry, sorry, I'm sorry.
わぁ、これラミィ、これラミィ！
Wah, this is Lamy, this is Lamy!
あ、ラミィだよ！
Ah, it's Lamy!
ありがとう！サンキュー！オープンシーズニィーキー！たぐらち、たぐらちだよ！
Thank you! Thank you! Open Season Nikki! Takurachi, it's Takurachi!
あ、 Do you want to say your 自己紹介 in English? I'm Hololive JP 5th Generation and Liver Face 1 Lamy!
Ah, do you want to say your self-introduction in English? I'm Hololive JP 5th Generation and Liver Face 1 Lamy!
ラミィ！ラミィ！イェーイ！
Lamy! Lamy! Yay!
Thanks for calling me! Congratulations on your 3D debut! Oh, omedetou! Arigatou!
Thanks for calling me! Congratulations on your 3D debut! Oh, congratulations! Thank you!
I took the liberty of drawing you.ちゃんと、ちゃんとハグ、ハグ、ハグ、ハグミー、ハグミー。う、ちゅ、ちゅ、もらった。うふふふふ。
I took the liberty of drawing you. Proper—proper hug, hug, hug, hug me, hug me. Woo, chu, chu, received. Hehehehe.
よかったよ！
I'm so glad!
もう、あれ、あの、おくらば、おくらば…
Wait, um, Okuraba, Okuraba...
しよう！しよう！
Let's do it! Let's do it!
日本酒！
Sake!
そうそうそう、ラミィの、あの...
That's right, Lamy's, um...
飲みたい！飲みたい！
I want to drink! I want to drink!
清酒！
Refined sake!
うんうんうん、わあ、飲みたい！
Yeah yeah yeah, wow, I want to drink!
かかもほん...お、かもほん、行く！
Kakamohon... Oh, kakamohon, let's go!
行く！行く！行く！あははは、行く！
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Ahahaha, let's go!
じゃあね、がんばってね！
Well then, do your best!
がんばってね！バイバイ！
Do your best! Bye-bye!
さっきのラミィ！
Lamy from earlier!
Lamy...
Oh, she's so cute.
I can't handle it. She's adorable, adorable.
I can't wait. I really want to try her sake, you know,
but you can't really buy it anymore because it's so popular.
But since, you know, I can just shimmy over to Lamy's place.
All right, all right, all right. How about one more?
One more member summoning? I realized that I need to draw a lot more detailed, you know,
in order to summon them, so maybe, you know,
I can do a special summon this time. I can do this. Okay, grab my brush.
Okay. I can already imagine her. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, and I can't forget the little accessory here.
Uh, like that, and that, and... yeah. And done!
All right. This one took a little longer, but... definitely detailed enough.
Who could it be? Hmm... It's not Yagoo.
Hi Yagoo!
Let me put down my brush. Whoa.
Who could it be? There's a watermelon, and some horns, flower in her hair...
our fluffy, fluffy senpai.
Okay, let's go call her in the special summoning room. I got to run.
え？何？
Eh? What?
え？何？角焼き食べたでなんだけど。
Eh? What? I was eating grilled mutton though.
え？え？
Eh? Eh?
おためせんぱい？
Watame-senpai?
あいえ、えっと、たこやきなう。
No, um, Takoyaki now.
お、たこ焼き、食べてたんだしか？食べてた。
Oh, Takoyaki, you were eating it? I was eating it.
たこたち、たこやき... あれ？
Tako-tachi, takoyaki... Huh?
あれ？誰だ？
Huh? Who is it?
誰が... あれ？誰が、わため先輩に食べられた？
Who... Huh? Who was eaten by Watame-senpai?
フー・ガ・インバート
Who got invited? Watame-senpai!
食べてやったし。
I ate 'em up!
せんぱい！いぇーい！
Senpai! Yay!
きゅう・り・でぃー！
3D!
うれしー！
So happy!
ビッグフェイス... あ、スモールフェイス？
Big face... Ah, small face?
の、の、の、の。キュートフェイス。
N-n-n-no. Cute face.
キュート。比べてみようよ。
Cute. Let's compare.
アドラブル。
Adorable.
いや、もう、もう同じ、等身ですか？
No, are we the same proportions?
同じだね。
They're the same.
うん、同じですよね。
Yeah, they're the same, right?
うんうんうん、うれしい！
Yeah yeah yeah, I'm so happy!
うれしい！
I'm so happy!
おめでとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
かわいいね。
So cute.
これ、わため先輩は割と、割とじゃないよね？
Watame-senpai is quite... well, isn't she?
わためろんも... え？
Watamelon too... Eh?
わためろんも...
Watamelon too...
うれしい！そして、わため先輩もあのライブの衣装で、なんか...
I'm so happy! And Watame-senpai also has that live outfit, like...
ガーター見たい。
Like a garter belt.
え？うん。なんで呼んでくれたの？
Eh? Yeah. Why did you call me?
いや、ちょっと、なんかスペシャルな日なので...
Well, it's a special day, so...
あの、できたら、わため先輩と会いたくて。
Um, if possible, I wanted to meet Watame-senpai.
うれしい！うれしい！
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
ぷりーず、しょうみー、わんきーぱい！
Please show me wackypai!
わっきーぱい？
Wackypai?
わっきーぱい！
Wackypai!
しょうみーわっきーぱい！わっきーぱい！
Show me wackypai! Wackypai!
わためせんぱい、わっきーぱいも... サンキュー！
Watame-senpai, wackypai too... Thank you!
サンキュー！
Thank you!
さすがに、わため先輩はわっきーぱいでした。
As expected, Watame-senpai was wackypai.
サンキュー！うれしい！きてくださってありがとうございます！
Thank you! I'm so happy! Thank you for coming!
こちらこそ！遊びましょう！わため先輩ためように！たこぱしましょう！
Likewise! Let's play! For Watame-senpai! Let's have a takoyaki party!
めて待てろよ！またね！びっくり待ってね！
Wait for me! See you! Wait a surprise!
My heart's beating not from the running
but from how cute they are, honestly.
I can't believe I finally got to meet them on a special day, too!
It's a happy, happy day!
But yeah, you know, um, I think the summoning canvas, special magical canvas worked really well,
but, you know, what if...
We also drew something different, like maybe a new stage, new place.
Do you think it'll work?
Well, we'll never know until we try, so let's give it a try, shall we?
All right, let's, get my brush.
This might take a little longer cause, um, not very good at drawing backgrounds yet, I think, but...
Oishou, co co co co co co co...
Heave-ho, co-co-co-co-co-co-co...
Co co co co co co...
Co-co-co-co-co-co...
Co co co...
Co-co-co...
All right, we have to be as detailed as possible, and done!
Done.
Um, can you guys guess? Guess the, guess the stage?
It's pretty good. I mean, it's the best I can do with this brush.
That's right. That's right. Okay, let me just put down this brush.
Okay, well, we'll see where this, uh, takes us.
I don't know if it's gonna work, but...
We'll see, all right.
Shall we, walking over to the summoning room. E ton ton ton ton ton ton...
I should not...
I shouldn't have...
Okay.
Running up the stairs is such hard work. Okay.
One last time, kakiba!
Didoo!
ユラリ ユルレル
Yurari yurureru,
泡沫 想い 廻る 称
transient thoughts revolving on the scales,
伝わる 水脈
connecting the water veins,
その手が 拓く 未来は
the future opened by those hands
光へ 手を伸ばす
reaches out toward the light.
ゆらり揺るれり 歌方想ひ
Gently swaying, the song's thoughts...
廻る秤
weight on the shifting scales.
伝ふ水脈
Tracing the water's veins,
その手が拓く 未来は
the future your hands will open up...
光へ手を伸ばす
reaches out to the light.
穢れなき銀の剣
An untarnished silver blade,
微苦笑ひ
a fleeting smile...
想ひを断ち切りて
cutting away all thoughts.
歌ふ静穏
Singing a solemn elegy...
水晶 柔く 光散りて
Soft crystal light scattering away,
闇の去り行く 暁
the dawn where darkness fades.
独り想ふ
Lost in thoughts all alone...
ゆらり揺るれり 歌方想ひ
Gently swaying, the song's thoughts...
廻る秤
weight on the shifting scales.
ゆらり揺るれり
Gently swaying, swaying,
歌方想ひ 廻る秤
thoughts of the song, the turning scales...
伝ふ水脈
Tracing the water's veins,
その手が拓く 未来は
the future your hands will open up...
光り散りて
light scattering away,
闇へと進みゆく
moving on into the darkness.
独り想ふ
Lost in thoughts all alone...
虚ろな白亜の王座
An empty white throne,
己をすべてを欺いて
deceiving oneself and everything...
紡ぐ理
weaving the truth.
黒白 混ざり
Black and white intertwining,
崩れ落ちて
crumbling down,
光去り行く 黄昏
dusk where light fades away.
独り想ふ
Lost in thoughts all alone...
選りし正しき道
The path you choose and walk upon...
嘆きも笑顔も
All of your sighs and your smiles,
悔いも夢も きっと
even your regrets and dreams...
行く末に迷い疲れ
Weary of hesitation at the end of the road,
流離い
drifting away...
古きは誰か知りや
Within my ancient heart dwells madness and pride...
ゆらり揺るれり
Gently swaying, swaying,
歌方想ひ 廻る秤
thoughts of the song, the turning scales...
伝ふ水脈
Tracing the water's veins,
その手が拓く 未来は
the future your hands will open up...
独り想ふ
Lost in thoughts all alone...
ふるれい ゆらり
Furu-re-i, yurari...
I guess we succeeded in summoning the new stage! Yay!
How was the song? Is the stage so, so pretty?
Yeah, oh my goodness. I was very nervous, but I pulled it off! I did it! Yay!
Yeah, oh my goodness. I was very nervous,
but I pulled it off! I did it! Yay!
Well, I have another song for you here, but we're going to have to change things a little bit.
Well, I have another song for you here,
but we're going to have to change things a little bit.
Whoa! It worked!
Okay, this place might be really familiar for you guys. I hope you like the next song.
Okay, this place might be really familiar for you guys.
I hope you like the next song.
Yeah, okay.
教えて 教えてよ
Tell me, please tell me,
その仕組みを
what this plot is all about.
ぼくの中に 誰がいるの？
Exactly, who resides within me?
壊れた 壊れたよ 壊れた世界で
I'm broken, so broken - amidst this world.
君が笑う 何も見えずに
Yet you laugh, blind to everything
壊れた僕なんてさ
Being as broken as I am,
息を止めて
I hold my breath.
ほどけない もう ほどけないよ 真実さえ freeze
And it can't be unraveled... Not even the truth. Freeze.
壊せる 壊せない
Breakable, unbreakable,
狂える 狂えない あなたを見つけて 揺れた
psychotic, unable to go insane.
I'll find you, and...
歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は透き通って見えなくなって
In this shaken, twisted world, I gradually become transparent
見ないでで ぼくのことを 見つめないでで
Please don't bother looking for me; don't stare at me.
誰かが描いた世界の中で あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
Inside a world someone imagined, I don't want to hurt you.
覚えていて ぼくのことを 鮮やかなまま
So please remember me, as vivid as I was.
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる 無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
Infinitely spreading solitude wraps around me.
Memories of times I laughed innocently come to mind.
動けない 動けない 動けない 動けない 動けない 動けないよ
And I can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, I cannot move!
unravelling the world
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
I've changed; I couldn't go back to the way I was.
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
As the two twine around one another, both of us will perish away...
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない あなたを汚さないよ 揺れた
Breakable, unbreakable, psychotic, unable to go insane.
I can't afford to let you be defiled!
歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は透き通って見えなくなって
In this shaken, twisted world, I gradually become transparent
見ないでで ぼくのことを 見つめないでで
Please don't bother looking for me; don't stare at me.
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に 未来がほどけてしまう前に
Before the future comes unraveled in a lonely trap someone laid out
思い出して ぼくのことを 鮮やかなまま
Please remember me, as vivid as I was.
忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで
Don't forget me, don't forget me, don't forget me, don't forget me!
変わってしまったことに paralyze 変えられないことだらけの paradise
Paralyzed by the fact that I've changed,
in a paradise filled with unrecoverable things.
覚えていて ぼくのことを
Please remember me...
教えて 教えて
Tell me, please tell me,
ぼくの中に 誰がいるの？
exactly who resides within me?
壊れた 壊れたよ 壊れた世界で 君が笑う 何も見えずに
I'm broken, so broken - amidst this world. Yet you laugh, blind to everything
忘れないで
Don't forget me,
don't forget me,
忘れないで
don't forget me!
私まがったことに paralyze 変えられないことだらけの paradise
Paralyzed by the fact that I've changed,
in a paradise filled with unrecoverable things.
覚えていて ぼくのことを
Please remember me...
教えて 教えてよ
Tell me, please tell me,
その仕組みを
what this plot is all about.
ぼくの中に 誰がいるの？
Exactly, who resides within me?
舞い雪は 星の欠片 天体に手を伸ばして
The fluttering snowflakes are stars' shards, reaching out to the celestial bodies,
行き交う願い感じているね すべては今 モノクロームの中
feeling our crossing wishes, everything is now in monochrome.
そっとこぼれた白い息 伝えたい言葉のかたち
The soft, spilled white breath, the shape of the words I wanted to convey,
きっと温もりのぶんだけ 空はほんのり明るくなった
surely, just by its warmth, the sky grew faintly brighter.
その背中をおし出会い それは望んだイニシエーション
Pushing that back, our encounter was the initiation I wished for.
じっと闇 目をこらす 孤独はもう終わっていた
Staring fixedly into the darkness, the loneliness was already over.
モノクローム ~version de l'apprivoiser~
[Title: Monochrome ~version de l'apprivoiser~]
そっとこぼれた白い息
The soft, spilled white breath,
伝えたかった言葉のかたち
the shape of the words I wanted to convey,
きっと温もりのぶんだけ
surely, just by its warmth,
空はほんのり明るくなった
the sky grew faintly brighter.
悲しみに濡れた翼
Wings soaked in sorrow,
重なり合う純白へ
toward overlapping pure white,
渡し合った未来への優しい勇気
gentle courage toward the future we handed to each other,
誰もしらない世界の夜明けを待っている鼓動
a heartbeat awaiting the dawn of an unknown world,
光を連れて旅立つ私にはじまる明日
a new tomorrow beginning within me as I set journey with light.
舞い雪は 星の欠片 天体に手を伸ばして
The fluttering snowflakes are stars' shards, reaching out to the celestial bodies,
行き交う願い 信じているね すべては今 モノクロームの中
believing in our crossing wishes, everything is now in monochrome.
凍えた記憶を解かす 手に入れた愛と共に
Defrosting frozen memories, together with the love we obtained,
振り返りずに感じ合おう 空の彼方
let's sense each other without looking back, beyond the sky.
それぞれが辿る軌道 たとえもう会えなくても
Each following our own trajectories, even if we can never meet again,
光が見える銀河のどこかでつながっているね
we are connected somewhere in the galaxy where light is visible.
散る星は砂のように また胸を優しく撫でる
The scattering stars, like sand, tenderly caress my chest again.
静かに眠る夢の残像 すべてはまだ モノクロームの中
The afterimage of a dream sleeping quietly, everything is still in monochrome.
舞う雪は 星の欠片 天体に 手をのばして
The fluttering snowflakes are pieces of stars, reaching out to the heavens,
行き交う願い 感じているね
Feeling the wishes crossing paths,
すべては今 モノクロームの中
All is now within the monochrome.
Yay! I did it!
What do you guys think? Got prepared three songs for you guys! Yay!
What do you guys think? I prepared three songs for you guys! Yay!
Thank you, thank you!
It's finally almost over, huh.
We waited over two, is it years?
We planned it out, but then you know, we had to wait so long, but
I worked so, so, so hard to make this happen,
and to actually dance it and sing it like a, like, good live!
and to actually dance and sing it like a... a proper live!
It was all worth it, it was all worth it.
What do you guys think? Did you guys like it? Do you guys like this stage?
Is this so cool? We're in space! We're in space!
Yeah, this is a special stage for a special occasion, so hope you guys like it.
Yeah, this is a special stage for a special occasion, so I hope you guys like it.
Thank you, thank you, everyone, thanks for coming to watch today.
Yeah, oh, I can't believe...
you know, it's I'm still processing it in my head how...
you know, I'm still processing it in my head how...
it's finally today.
Oh, I'm going to cry. Don't don't cry, don't cry!
No, no leaking ceilings, it's okay. Woo!
But yeah, you know, um, without everyone, you know, um, you guys,
Mitz, all the staff, all the studio staff, thank you so, so much for...
making this happen, and Naitchan...
Oh yeah, thank you, thank you so, so, so much.
Oh, you know, um, no, no leaking ceilings.
We got we got business here for this special occasion, you know,
We got business here for this special occasion, you know.
I believe it's time to maybe announce some, you know, goods and stuff, maybe maybe maybe.
You guys ready? Ready?
Taco, Taco, what are you doing here, Taco?
Oh, you're not supposed to... Oh, you're not supposed to come up here on the stage, Taco!
Oh, you were worried. Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay. Don't don't cry, Taco. Be happy.
Wait, what?
You you want to become the merch?
Are are you sure about that? Are you sure?
Okay, I mean, if you're fine with it. Well, Taco, yoish!
Well, with this noble Taco sacrifice, we shall treat new merch for this special occasion!
Are you guys ready? All right, Taco, are you ready?
You're not worrying, you know? Okay. Okay.
One, two, three, no! I think I, yeah, I think I did it.
Okay.
All right. You guys ready? Are you ready? All right.
And ta-da!
That's right. Taco, you're, you're squished! What happened?
Taco, are you okay? Taco's okay.
Stop, stuck on my hand. Wait, I need to get off, get off.
Okay, maybe not. Okay, this Taco's stuck on my hand. But
the goods for this special occasion will be
a Takodachi Ramen Stopper, "Let's TAKO a break"!
Okay, Taco, you can go back now. Whew, whew, whew, whew.
Ah, that's right. For all you cup noodle enjoyers, you can now have a personal Takodachi to help you hold the lid down in place.
Or it can be a cute little figure, too. That's also a possibility.
Yeah, I actually, you know, played around with it and you can kind of like push it, push the taco down and like sticks onto your hand. It's very nice.
Yeah, I actually, you know, played around with it and you can kind of like push it, push the taco down and like it sticks onto your hand. It's very nice.
But yeah, this will go on sale, not today, not today. Remember that, this will go on sale starting March 5th.
Batch five.
It's holoMyth 3D collab.
So after that, after everyone's is over,
it's going to go on sale.
So please look forward to it.
I hope you guys like it.
Oh, it's so cute.
But yeah,
one more thing, one more thing, one more thing,
is actually tonight. Tonight.
Around, what, five hours or so from now, it's gonna be
my real hologram debut. Woo!
It's gonna be a hologram!
Yeah, apparently there's gonna be a lot of tentacles,
so I hope you guys look forward to it.
Yeah.
Ah, it's been, it's been an amazing time, everyone.
Thank you so much again.
And make sure you check out everyone in Myth's 3D showcases too.
Next up is Kiara. Kiara, that's you. That's you.
But yes. Uh and then
it's gonna be Calli and then Gura and then Amelia and then the collab.
It's gonna be such a fun month.
Anyways, thank you so much again, everyone, for being patient and waiting. It's finally here.
And I'll continue to do my best. Yes.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
This is it. Bye-bye.